https://www.schgroup.com/legal-disclaimer/

Legal Disclaimer SC&H Group, Inc., an accounting firm, is the parent company. Investment advisory services are offered through SC&H Financial Advisors, Inc. SC&H Financial Advisors, Inc. is a wholly owned subsidiary of SC&H Group, Inc.   Broker-dealer services are offered through Stout Causey Capital Corporation. These entities are affiliated entities that share common control of the parent company, but are separate entities.LEGAL DISCLAIMERIn the preparation of this site, every effort has been made to offer the most current, correct, and clearly expressed information possible. Nonetheless, inadvertent errors can occur, and applicable laws, rules, and regulations often change.Copyright © 2020 SC&H Group, Inc. All rights reserved. No part of the text or graphics on this site may be reproduced or transmitted in any form or by any means, electronic or mechanical, including by photocopying, facsimile transmission, recording, rekeying, or using any information storage and retrieval system, without permission in writing from SC&H Group, Inc.Certain links on this site lead to resources located on servers maintained by third parties over whom SC&H Group, Inc. has no control. As such, SC&H Group, Inc. makes no representation as to the accuracy or any other aspect of the information contained on such servers.Portal End User License AgreementIMPORTANT — READ CAREFULLY: Welcome to the SC&H Group Portal (the “SC&H Portal” or the “Portal”). By clicking the “Yes” button, the user (“You”) agree(s) to be bound by the terms and conditions contained in this agreement (the “Agreement”) and the terms and conditions of SC&H’s privacy notice.  The privacy notice explains how SC&H treats your personal information, and protects your privacy, when you use the SC&H Portal.  SC&H may change the terms of this Agreement and/or the privacy notice from time to time without notice to you, and you are responsible for the then current version of the policies in effect at all times.  If you do not agree to be bound by these terms and conditions or privacy notice policies, you may not use the SC&H Portal.ModificationsYou agree that we may modify this Agreement or any policy or other terms referenced in this Agreement at any time and at our sole discretion. By using the SC&H Portal, you agree to be bound by any such modifications and should therefore periodically visit this page and the SC&H Portal to determine the then current terms and conditions of use to which you are bound. You will note that at the bottom of this Agreement, the date of last modification is indicated. You are encouraged to check the revision date with each use to ensure you are comfortable with the latest revisions.  If you are dissatisfied with the SC&H Portal site, its content or this Agreement as it may be revised, you agree that your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the Portal.TerminationYou agree that SC&H may terminate this Agreement, for any reason at our sole discretion, at any time, without notice, and that SC&H reserves the right to change, suspend, or discontinue all or any aspects of the SC&H Portal, for any reason at our sole discretion, at any time, without noticeUser RestrictionsYou agree that:You will not tamper with or otherwise interfere or attempt to interfere in any manner with the functionality or proper working of the Portal.You will not make illegal use of the Portal or use it for purposes which are illegal.You will not interfere with anyone else who is a user of the Portal in their use of the Portal.You will follow U.S. and international laws regarding transmitting data and you will not attempt to gain access to our computer system or any other computer systems.You will not remove, obscure, or alter any notice of any logo, trademark, or other intellectual property or proprietary right designation appearing on or contained within the portal.You will not access (or attempt to access) any product or services offered via the SC&H Portal by any means other than the interface that is provided by SC&H.You will not upload, post, transmit, or store any material that:is unlawful, offensive, defamatory, fraudulent, deceptive, misleading, harmful, threatening, harassing, obscene, or objectionable;breaches any of your contractual or confidentiality obligations;disrupts or interferes with the normal operations of the Site, such as posting or transmitting viruses, continuous posting of repetitive materials, or posting and/or uploading abnormally large files or other data; oris an advertisement or other solicitation, including, but not limited to, any unauthorized advertising materials, unsolicited promotional materials, “junk mail,” “spam mail,” “chain letters,” “pyramid schemes,” franchises, distributorships, club memberships, sales arrangements, or similar materials;You will not violate other’s privacy rights or personal rights by abusing the Materials, including, but not limited to, harassing or “stalking” another person, sending unsolicited e-mails, or collecting other’s personal information;You will not breach or attempt to breach any security measures of the Site;You will not use any device, process, or mechanism (e.g., a spider or “bot”) to monitor, retrieve, search, or access the Site or any Material without our prior written consent;You will not access or attempt to access any account or login of any other user or third party listed on the Site;You will not copy, modify, reproduce, delete, distribute, download, store, transmit, sell, re-sell, publish, reverse engineer, or create derivative works of any Materials;You will not post or submit any inaccurate, false, or incomplete information;You will not impersonate any person or entity;You will not forge any header information in any electronic posting or mail;You will not misrepresent yourself, your affiliation with any third party, or your entity.Passwords You agree and understand that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of passwords associated with any account you use to access the SC&H Portal.  Accordingly, you agree that you are solely responsible to SC&H for all activities that occur under your account.  If you become aware of any unauthorized use of your password on the SC&H Portal or your account, you agree to notify SC&H immediately at portaladmin@schgroup.com.CCH ProSystem fx Master Software License Agreement  You are hereby notified that in connection with providing access to you to the SC&H Portal and services related thereto, SC&H has entered into a Software License Agreement with CCH Incorporated, a Wolters Kluwer business (“CCH”), a copy of which is located here: http://support.cch.com/uploads/CCH%20Profx%20Software%20License%20Agreement.pdf  (“CCH Software License Agreement”).  You hereby agree that you shall thoroughly and completely review the terms of the CCH Software License Agreement, and that you shall use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that your use of the SC&H Portal will not cause or result in any violation of you as “Client” or SC&H as “Customer” under the terms of the CCH Software License Agreement.Monitoring We reserve the right to log, review, and otherwise examine any information stored on or passing through our networks or systems.Downtime and Service Suspensions Your access to and use of the Services may be suspended for the duration of any anticipated, unanticipated, scheduled or unscheduled downtime, maintenance, system updates, malfunction, or other unavailability of any portion or all of the Services for any reason, including as a result of power outages, system failures or other interruptions.We shall also be entitled, without any liability to you, to suspend access to any portion or all of the Portal at any time, on a system-wide basis: (a) for scheduled downtime to permit us to conduct maintenance or make modifications to any Portal; (b) in the event of a denial of service attack or other attack on the Portal or other event that we determine, in our sole discretion, may create a risk to the applicable Portal, to you or to any of our other customers if the Portal service were not suspended; or (c) in the event that we determine that any Portal service is prohibited by law or we otherwise determine that it is necessary or prudent to do so for legal or regulatory reasons.Rights to Use of SC&H Portal SC&H grants you a personal, non-assignable and non-exclusive license to use the SC&H Portal as part of the services being provided to you by SC&H.  This license is for the sole purpose of enabling you to use and enjoy the benefit of the SC&H Portal and services, in the manner permitted by these terms and conditions.  You may not, and you may not permit anyone else to, copy, modify, create a derivative work of, reverse engineer, decompile or otherwise attempt to extract the source code of the SC&H Portal or any part thereof. Except as expressly provided herein, unless SC&H has given you specific written permission to do so, you may not assign (or grant a sub-license of) your rights to use the SC&H Portal, grant a security interest in or over your rights to use the SC&H Portal, or otherwise transfer any part of your rights to use the SC&H Portal.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, you are granted limited administrative rights to provide access to the SC&H Portal in your reasonable discretion to those parties who would reasonably need to access information located on the SC&H Portal, or who could upload information and documents (such as tax documents and other financial papers) onto the SC&H Portal for you to access, that would assist you in utilizing the services provided by the SC&H Portal in the ordinary course.Intellectual Property  The content on the SC&H Portal including without limitation, the text, software, scripts, graphics, photos, sounds, videos, interactive features and the like (“Content”) and the trademarks, service marks and logos contained therein (“Marks”), are owned by or licensed to SC&H, subject to copyright and other intellectual property rights under United States and foreign laws and international conventions. Content on the SC&H Portal is provided to you AS IS for your information and personal use only and may not be used, copied, reproduced, distributed, transmitted, broadcast, displayed, sold, licensed, or otherwise exploited for any other purposes whatsoever without the prior written consent of the respective owners. SC&H reserves all rights not expressly granted in and to the SC&H Portal and the Content. You agree to not engage in the use, copying, or distribution of any of the Content other than expressly permitted herein. If you download or print a copy of the Content for personal use, you must retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained therein. You agree not to circumvent, disable or otherwise interfere with security-related features of the SC&H Portal or features that prevent or restrict use or copying of any Content or enforce limitations on use of the SC&H Portal or the Content therein.Copyright and Trademark policies It is SC&H’s policy to respond to notices of alleged copyright infringement that comply with applicable international intellectual property law (including, without limitation, in the United States, the Digital Millennium Copyright Act) and to terminating the accounts of repeat infringers.Other Content The SC&H Portal may include hyperlinks to other web sites or content or resources that are not owned or controlled by SC&H.  SC&H has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party web sites or resources which are provided by companies or persons other than SC&H.  You acknowledge and agree that SC&H is not responsible for the availability of any such external sites or resources, and does not endorse any advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such web sites or resources.  You acknowledge and agree that SC&H is not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products, or other materials on, or available from, such web sites or resources.  We encourage you to be aware when you leave the SC&H Portal and to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of each other website that you visit.Disclaimer YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND ACCEPT THAT: (I) YOU ASSUME ALL RISKS RELATED TO OR RESULTING FROM YOUR USAGE, VIEWING, OR ACCESS OF THE SITE AND ITS MATERIALS. THE SITE AND ITS MATERIALS ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND AN “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. (II) WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, OR WARRANTIES ARISING FROM COURSE OF PERFORMANCE, COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE. (III) WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES (A) THAT THE SITE AND ITS MATERIALS WILL BE ERROR-FREE OR VIRUS-FREE; (B) THAT THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED AND SECURE; (C) THAT THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS; AND (D) REGARDING THE RELIABILITY, ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, VALIDITY, TIMELINESS OR TRUTHFULNESS OF ANY SUBMITTED INFORMATION. ANY MATERIALS DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED IS DONE SO AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK, AND YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIALS.Liability and Limitations of Liability YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT THE SITE AND ITS MATERIALS ARE NOT A SUBSTITUTE FOR PROFESSIONAL ADVICE. YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT SOME LAWS, REGULATIONS, GUIDELINES AND OTHER MATTERS ADDRESSED IN THE SITE AND ITS MATERIALS ARE SUBJECT TO INTERPRETATION AND THAT YOU SHALL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR, AND WAIVE ANY CLAIM AGAINST US, OUR PARENTS, AND SUBSIDIARIES, AND THEIR RESPECTIVE AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, AGENTS, AND EMPLOYEES FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGE AND EXPENSE OR CLAIM THEREOF) RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND ITS MATERIALS. YOU AGREE THAT THE AVAILABILITY OF THE SITE AND ITS MATERIALS SHALL NOT BE CONSTRUED AS THE RENDERING OF ANY TAX, LEGAL, ATTEST, ACCOUNTING, AUDITING OR OTHER PROFESSIONAL, SERVICES OR ADVICE.YOU AGREE TO ASSUME ALL RISKS ASSOCIATED WITH, ARISING OUT OF, OR RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF THE SITE, THE MATERIALS, OR ANY SUBMITTED INFORMATION, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE RISKS OF FINANCIAL LOSS, PHYSICAL HARM, PROPERTY DAMAGES, DEALING WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SITE, STRANGERS, MINORS, OR FOREIGN NATIONALS, AND PERSONS ACTING UNDER FALSE PRETENSE. YOU FURTHER AGREE TO RELEASE US, OUR PARENTS, AND AFFILIATES, AND THEIR RESPECTIVE AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, AGENTS, AND EMPLOYEES, HARMLESS FROM ALL CLAIMS, DEMANDS, DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, REVENUE, DATA, OR USE, INCURRED BY YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION IN CONTRACT, TORT, OR BREACH OR FAILURE OF WARRANTY, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES) OF ANY KIND OR NATURE, KNOWN OR UNKNOWN, ASSOCIATED WITH, ARISING OUT OF, OR RESULTING FROM YOUR USAGE OF THE SITE, THE MATERIALS, ANY SUBMITTED INFORMATION, AND ANY TRANSACTIONS RELATED TO OR RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OF THE SITE. IF YOU ARE A CALIFORNIA RESIDENT, YOU WAIVE CALIFORNIA CIVIL CODE §1542, WHICH STATES: “A GENERAL RELEASE DOES NOT EXTEND TO CLAIMS WHICH THE CREDITOR DOES NOT KNOW OR SUSPECT TO EXIST IN HIS FAVOR AT THE TIME OF EXECUTING THE RELEASE, WHICH IF KNOWN BY HIM MUST HAVE MATERIALLY AFFECTED HIS SETTLEMENT WITH THE DEBTOR.”NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING TO THE CONTRARY HEREIN, YOU AGREE AND ACKNOWLEDGE THAT OUR AGGREGATE LIABILITY FOR ANY DAMAGES SHALL NOT EXCEED U.S. $10.You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold us, our parents, and subsidiaries, and their respective affiliates, officers, directors, agents, employees, harmless from any claims or demands of any third party, including, but not limited to, attorneys’ fees and legal fees, resulting from or arising out of your Use of the Site, your Use of the Materials, your Submitted Information, or your violation of any terms and conditions of this Notice.Notices All Notices by us to you shall be by email to the email address listed as the Portal Administrator.All notices by you to us shall be by email to portaladmin@schgroup.com or in writing to:SC&H Group, Inc. 910 Ridgebrook Road Sparks, MD 21152Entire Agreement  This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and us regarding the subject matter hereof and supersedes any and all prior or contemporaneous representation, understanding, agreement, or communication between you and us, whether written or oral, regarding such subject matter.Severability If any portion of this Agreement is held by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid or unenforceable, the remaining portions of this Agreement will remain in full force and effect, and any invalid or unenforceable portions shall be construed in a manner that most closely reflects the effect and intent of the original language. If such construction is not possible, the provision will be severed from this Agreement, and the rest of the Agreement shall remain in full force and effect.Waivers The failure by us to enforce any provision of this Agreement shall in no way be construed to be a present or future waiver of such provision nor in any way affect our right to enforce such provision thereafter. All waivers by us must be in writing to be effective.Successors and Assigns This Agreement will be binding upon, and inure to the benefit of the parties and their respective successors and assigns.Assignment This Agreement, and any rights and licenses granted hereunder, may not be transferred or assigned by you, but may be assigned by SC&H without restriction.Relationship Nothing in this Agreement is intended to or does create any type of joint venture, creditor-debtor, escrow, partnership or any employer/employee or fiduciary or franchise relationship between you and us (or any of our Associates).Governing Law  This Agreement shall be construed and enforced according to the laws of the State of Maryland applicable to agreements made and to be performed wholly within the State of Maryland.  You agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located within the State of Maryland, County of Baltimore, to resolve any legal matter arising from these terms and conditions.  Notwithstanding this, you agree that SC&H shall still be entitled to apply for any necessary injunctive remedies in any jurisdiction.Termination We shall have the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate any services of the Site and remove any Materials from the Site. We may also terminate your access to any part or all of the services provided by us on the Site at any time, with or without cause or notice, for any or no reason. We shall not be responsible for maintaining or returning your Submitted Information.Last Revision Date This Agreement was last revised on March 2, 2018.Privacy Notice CPAs, like all providers of personal financial services, are now required by law to inform their clients of their policies regarding privacy of client information. CPAs have been and continue to be bound by professional standards of confidentiality that are even more stringent than those required by law. Therefore, we have always protected your right to privacy.This privacy notice outlines the policies and practices for SC&H Group, Inc. (“SC&H”) and any and all domain names, web portals and web sites owned and operated by SC&H, including www.schgroup.com (collectively, the “SC&H Portal”).  The SC&H Portal may contain links to websites operated by third parties and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites.In order to use the SC&H Portal, you are required to review these policies.  By using the SC&H Portal or communicating with us by e-mail, you agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy and to the terms of use of the SC&H Portal (set forth in the “Agreement”). By using the SC&H Portal or visiting any web site owned or operated by SC&H, you hereby agree to be bound by the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Notice, and by the terms and conditions of SC&H’s end user license agreement (“EULA”).  The privacy notice explains how SC&H treats your personal information, and protects your privacy, when you use the SC&H Portal.  SC&H reserves the right to change the privacy notice and terms of the EULA at any time without notice. Any changes to the privacy notice or EULA shall be posted in this page and shall be effective immediately upon posting. If you do not agree to be bound by these privacy notice policies and EULA, you may not use the SC&H Portal.Types Of Nonpublic Personal Information We CollectWe collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:Information we receive from you on applications or other formsInformation about your transactions with usInformation we receive from others that you have sent to usOur Web server automatically records the IP addresses of visitors to our site. This information is used in aggregate form to help us understand how visitors use the SC&H Portal. The servers at the SC&H Portal web site also collect connection-related technical data. The data entries in these logs are used for server and network operation and maintenance and to help us understand general usage patterns. No personally identifiable information is collected unless you knowingly provide it.Use of data collected Nonpublic personal data about you collected may be used for editorial and feedback purposes, marketing and promotional purposes, statistical analysis of users’ behavior, product development, content and layout improvement, and to inform advertisers and business partners as to how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements. Information may also be made available to contractors as needed for maintenance of our systems / infrastructure.Parties To Whom We Disclose Information As part of our firm’s policy, we do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about current or former clients that is obtained in the course of our practice except as required or permitted by law. Permitted disclosures include, for instance, providing information to our employees and, in limited situations, to unrelated third parties who need to know that information to assist us in providing services to you.  In all such situations, we stress the confidential nature of information being shared.Use of Cookies We may use “cookies” on our websites to personalize and enhance your website visits. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by our web server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to a computer, and your computer will only allow our web servers to access our cookies. The most important thing to understand about cookies is that they pose no danger to you. They cannot be used to collect secret information about you or your computer or to provide information about you to other companies.Cookies provide a convenience by saving you time on subsequent visits and personalizing your web experience. For example, when you return to our website, cookies enable us to remember information from prior visits, and cookies may save data such as name, password, user-name, screen preferences, and pages viewed.You have the right to delete cookies placed on your hard drive, which will erase the data automatically saved during your visit. However that will mean that our sites will not recognize you when you return. You may also modify your web browser to notify you before accepting cookies, or to decline all cookies. We strongly suggest that you accept cookies from us, since they help provide you a more seamless, personalized, and effective web browsing experience and keep our site compelling and informative.Links to Other Web Sites The SC&H Portal or web site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by SC&H. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites. This privacy statement applies only to the SC&H Portal.Warranty Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability The SC&H Portal and its owner make no representation of any kind regarding the site content or any portion thereof. All site content is provided in “AS IS” condition, and the SC&H Portal and SC&H expressly disclaims any and all warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular use.Applicable Law and Jurisdiction The SC&H Portal, including www.schgroup.com web site (excluding links to web sites operated by others) is controlled and operated by SC&H from offices in and around Baltimore, Maryland. Although SC&H has made no effort to publish the SC&H Portal, including www.schgroup.com web site elsewhere, it is accessible in all fifty U.S. states and in other countries due to its presence on the Worldwide Web. As each of these states and countries have laws which may differ from those of Maryland and from each other, and as you and SC&H both benefit from establishing a predictable legal environment in which to publish, access and use the SC&H Portal, including www.schgroup.com web site, by publishing, accessing, and/or using the sites you agree that all matters arising from or relating to the use and operation of the sites will be governed by the laws of the State of Maryland, without regard to its conflict of laws principles. You agree that all claims you may have arising from or relating to the operation or use of the SC&H Portal, including www.schgroup.com web site will be heard and resolved in the courts of Baltimore County, Maryland. You consent to personal jurisdiction of such courts over you, stipulate to the fairness and convenience of proceeding in such courts, and covenant not to assert any objection to proceeding in such courts. If you choose to access the www.schgroup.com Web Site from locations other than Baltimore County, Maryland, you will be responsible for compliance with all local laws of such other locations.The SC&H Portal, including www.schgroup.com web site is confidential and proprietary to SC&H.  All of the text, images, marks, logos and other content of this Web Site is proprietary to SC&H or is used with the owner’s permission or applicable law or regulation.Personal Data Access and Correction. We will provide access to, update and amend, and/or delete the Personal Information in accordance with applicable law. You can request access to, and have the opportunity to update and amend your Personal Information, and, you can exercise the other rights acknowledged by applicable data protection legislation, including, for example, objection to and blocking of the processing of your Personal Information, by sending a letter to Attn: Database Management at the address set forth below.For security reasons, we reserve the right to take steps to authenticate the identity of the requesting party before providing access to Personal Information in accordance with this section of the Privacy Policy.Revisions to the Policy. If we change this Policy we will post any updates here for your review. If we change material terms in this Policy, we will provide notice of the revised policy for 30 days on the home page with a link back to this page. We will also take other steps as necessary depending on the nature of the changes, including obtaining your consent where required by local data protection laws, or providing you with the opportunity to delete your Personal Information.Mailing Address SC&H Group, Inc. 910 Ridgebrook Road Sparks, MD 21152Protecting the Confidentiality and Security of Current and Former Clients’ Information We retain records relating to professional services that we provide so that we are better able to assist you with your professional needs and, in some cases, to comply with professional guidelines. In order to guard your nonpublic personal information, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with our professional standards.We hope this information will provide better knowledge of our efforts to provide the best services to you. If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact our office.Very truly yours,SC&H GroupLast Revision Date  This Privacy Notice was last revised on April 28, 2020. Navigating Individual & Corporate Tax Planning Strategies in the New Era of Tax Reform
View the Webinar
An Executive’s Field Guide to Developing an Effective Cloud Strategy
Download Now
The Private Sector’s Quest for Enhanced Quality and Lower Costs
Get The Report
We've updated our Privacy Policy to give you more clarity over how we use cookies to collect and use your personal data to deliver a better experience. Please take a moment to read our Privacy Policy, and keep in mind that by continuing to access and utilize this website, you agree to the terms contained in these documents and also to our use of cookies as described in our Policy. You may unsubscribe at any time using the "Unsubscribe" link included in our emails.Accept and Close
